scc-fl.edu 2004-06-03

# SCC - Internet Privacy Policy

#### Internet Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting scc-fl.edu. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit Seminole Community College, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit scc-fl.edu, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved. This information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and your personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to an e-newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will only be used for the purposes you authorized. Some of this information may be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the state of Florida's archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law.

If you have other questions about the Seminole Community College privacy policies, or have suggestions on how these policies can be improved, please feel free to e-mail us at WebSupport@scc-fl.edu.

[Take Me Back](javascript:goBack\(\))  

Every reasonable effort has been made to ensure the accuracy of the content contained on this site.  However, we encourage you to contact the College, specific department, or instructor to verify that the information you have is current.
